# Recep Ahmet Saritekin

Mugla Sitki Kocman University Engineering Department Kotekli/Mugla

🛘 (+90) 537-247-9500 | 💌 rahmetsaritekin@gmail.com | 🖸 us | 🤡 saritekin | 📓 syny | 🛅 rahmetsaritekin | 💌 distortionalist

"We lay on our backs, looking at the ceiling and wondering what God had wrought when He made life so sad. Jack Kerouac-On The Road"

# **Summary**<sub>-</sub>

During my high school life I became an semi-expert in the Wing-Tsun that is a traditional Southern Chinese Kung-fu styles and I still use philosophy of Wing-Tsun in my life. I have played guitar and had a sing on my own and with many different music groups since high school. I have great interest in literature, philosophy, physics, mathematics and art. In general, I read, write, research and discuss. I'm traveling to Turkey, which is also the first goal with hitchhiking. I can stay on the road for a long time. My goal is not to arrive somewhere, I like the road itself, the blessings that the road offers me.

Currently, I am a third grade computer engineering student at Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University. I am someone who likes to solve problems in new ways and learn new technologies when needed. I've been learning new things by learning to learn for 3 years. I adopt free software philosophy and I like to contribute to open source projects in Github(tensorflow, jax, fastai, dffml, etc). Previously, I was working as a full-stack developer and a blockchain developer. The last summer I worked on TensorFlow with Google Brain Team on Google Summer of Code. Now I'm doing research on machine learning and deep learning of math. In my work environment, I use Vim, jetbrains IDE's, jupyter notebook, linux and OSX,

# Work Experience

#### Google Summer of Code < Tensor Flow >

CA, United States

INTERN

- May. 2019, 25 Aug. • I worked in the TensorFlow Dataset repository with Google Brain developers for 3 months.
- I added some new features, hunted bugs, reviewed pull requests, issues, etc.

Allonzi Istanbul, Turkey

**CREATOR & SOFTWARE DEVELOPER** 

· A social app that guides people on their journey.

**Inotek Robotic AR-GE** Mugla, Turkey

CREATOR & ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE RESEARCHER

Sep. 2017, PRESENT

Nov. 2017 - PRESENT

Nov. 2018, May. 2019

- · By collecting data from IOT devices in air, sea, air and forests, we need to determine the fire detection and so on.
- We are developing our own UAV (Unmanned Aerial Vehicle), drones and 3D printers.

Cryptouch Mugla, Turkey

CREATOR & BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

- Special communication application using blockchain and IPFS in infrastructure. • It has a distributed infrastructure focused on freedom, high security, scalability and permanency.
- Specific networks can be set up to certain people or individuals without external access.

**Speakmates** Tokyo, Japan

FREELANCER FULL STACK DEVELOPER & DJANGO DEVELOPER

Oct. 2017 - Jan. 2018

· A website that offers a platform where local or foreign language consultants and small groups of people who want to learn a foreign language can find each other and meet in comfortable places.

## Honors & Awards

2018	<b>Champion</b> , Genç Beyinler Yeni Fikirler Idea Competition	Izmir, Turkey
2013	<b>5nd</b> , Ankara Ataturk Marathon Run	Ankara, Turkey
2010	Finalist, Turkey Futsal Tournament	İstanbul, Turkey
2009	Champion, Table Tennis City Tournament	Düzce, Turkey

MARCH 3, 2020 RECEP A. SARITEKIN · RESUME **Presentation** 

#### Presentations contain stand-up and lots of information

**Developer Conference** Muğla, Turkey

SPEAKER < NEURAL NETWORKS AND DEEP LEARNING>

• I speak about basics of neural networks and modern deep learning applications.

Teknopark İzmir International Blockchain Workshop

SPEAKER < BLOCKCHAIN BASED SECURE COMMINICATION APPLICATION PROPOSAL: CRYPTOUCH>

• I speak about the advantages and business areas of my own project Cryptouch.

ISDFS 2018: 6th International Symposium on Digital Forensic and Security

SPEAKER < BLOCKCHAIN BASED SECURE COMMINICATION APPLICATION PROPOSAL: CRYPTOUCH>

• I explained my new project Cryptouch's security infrastructure in this conference.

**Developer Conference** Muğla, Turkey

SPEAKER <'TIR GIT> Feb 2018

· I speak about GIT(the version control system) infrastructure, explained the whole documentation in this conference.

### **Education**

#### MSKU (Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University Faculty of Engineering))

COMPUTER ENGINEERING UNDERGRADUATE EDUCATION

· I am trying to develop myself on the computer scienc by benefiting from the experiences of my teachers.

#### MSKU(Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University Faculty of Foreign Languages)

PREPARATORY EDUCATION

I received a one-year preparatory education for 100% English Computer Engineering department.

**Ankara Police Collage** Ankara, Turkey

High School Sep. 2011 - Exp. Apr. 2015

• I was educated until the third year as the last students of the College(it's a high school). Then it was closed because of political reasons.

# **Extracurricular Activity**

Zeki ve White Streets

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL

Jan. 2018 - PRESENT

Nov. 2018

İzmir, Turkey

Antalya, Turkey

Muğla, Turkey

Muğla, Turkey

Sep. 2016 - Aug. 2017

Sep. 2017 - Exp. Aug. 2021

May. 2018

Mar. 2018

· I am coming from metal guitar and I found a new friend who coming from classical guitar and we are create different taste improvisation musics that comes metal and classic touches and these are very absurd musics.

**Dertsiz Deli** 

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL Jan. 2017 - Dec. 2018

· Together with my vocalist friend, we try to mumbling little things and make music. We will share our musics in different social medias.

#### Düzce Anadolu Öğretmen High School Rock Band

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL

Düzce, Turkey Apr. 2015 - Jun. 2016

• We gave concerts at the festivals and graduations at high schools in Düzce.

#### **Ankara Police College Wing Tsun Team**

Ankara, Turkey Sep. 2012 - Apr.2015

**COACH ASSISTANT** 

• I would help the teacher during training, I would check and help my friends.

#### PKMG (Police College Rock Band)

Ankara, Turkey

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL Oct. 2013 - Apr. 2015

- · In the rock band of the school, I learned to be a team with my friends, to do something together and to produce new things.
- We attended the national high school music competition on behalf of our school.
- We gave small concerts in different places.

#### **Ankara Police College Athletics Team**

Ankara, Turkey

MIDDLE DISTANCE AND FLAG RUNNER

Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2013

· With our national instructor Adil and my friends, we participated in competitions and won prizes together for a year.